領 銜 主 演
艾 爾 · 帕 西 諾          羅 伯 特 · 德 尼 羅
片 名: 盜 火 線
又 譯: 烈 火 悍 將
編劇 及 導演
邁 克 爾 · 曼
Yeah, you can leave her in the hallway for now.
你現在可以把她留在走廊裏
- Stabilizing here. - Where's the portable x-ray?
- 穩住這兒  - 便攜X光機在哪兒
Check, charge or cash?
支票  信用卡  還是現金
Cash. And, uh...
現金
...make it out to Jack's Demolition, Tucson.
發票寫土珊市積氏拆卸公司
Seven eighty-eight thirty.
總數是七百八十八點三元
Okay.
好了
Hey.
嘿
Taking me to breakfast?
和我吃早餐嗎
I can't, I'm meeting Bosko.
不行  我得去見博高
Hey, Vincent.
嘿  雲信
- Mom, where are my barrettes? - Hi, sweetie.
- 媽媽  我的髮夾呢  - 嘿  寶貝
- I saw them on the kitchen table. - They're not there. I already checked.
- 我看見在廚房桌子上  - 不在那兒  我看過了
- Want me to make coffee? - No school today?
- 喝咖啡嗎  - 今天不用上學嗎
My dad's taking me to the new building and then to lunch.
爸爸帶我去新大廈  然後吃午餐
Try under the cushions on the sofa.
到沙發墊子下找
He's already a half an hour late.
他遲了半小時
He gonna show? Or that son of a bitch gonna stand her up like last time?
他會出現還是像上次那樣爽約
- I'll make coffee. - I'm out of time, babe.
- 我煮咖啡  - 沒時間了
Mom, where are my barrettes? They're not in the couch.
我的髮夾不在沙發里
Wear the blue ones.
戴藍色那一個
I don't wanna wear the blue ones. They don't match.
我不想戴  顏色不配襯
- Did you check in your bathroom? - I checked everywhere.
- 浴室找過沒有  - 找過了
- Well, what do you want me to do? - Find them.
- 我該怎辦  - 去找
- Mom, pay attention. - All right, sweetie, all right. What?
- 媽  留心  - 好了  寶貝
- Daddy's gonna be here. - Okay, he's gonna...
- 爸爸會到來的  - 好啦
I'm not gonna be ready. I can't be late.
我來不及準備  我可不能遲到
- You won't be late. - No, I will be late.
- 你不會遲到的  - 我會遲到的
Okay. Before Daddy comes, we can find them if we look together.
若一起找  爸到來前會找到
- It's all right, baby. It's all right. - No.
- 沒事的  寶貝  - 不
It's all right. It's all right.
沒事的
We'll find them together, you and me. We'll find them together.
我們一起找
Just relax. He won't come before we find them. I promise you.
放心  他到來前我們會找到
Hey. Give me another refill.
給我添一杯
Now he wants a refill.
再添一杯
- What's your name? - Waingro.
- 你叫什麼  - 榮谷
You're Michael, huh?
你是米高吧
You guys always work together?
你們常一起合作嗎
All the time.
經常合作
- Real tight crew, huh? - Real tight.
- 合作無間吧  - 是的
Yeah, if this works good, I'd consider going again, you know.
若今次順利  我會考慮再做
Yeah. Stop talking, okay, Slick?
好的  別再說話  滑頭
- How's he doing? - A hundred percent.
- 他怎麼樣  - 百分百滿意
Right on schedule.
很準時
Made a right on Venice Boulevard.
威尼斯街右轉
- We're a mile and a half from you. - Okay.
- 我們離你一英里半  - 好的
Just crossed over the number-one lane, 300 yards from you now.
越過行車快線  離你三百碼
- Get set. - I am.
- 準備  - 準備就緒
Put that on.
戴上面具
Here we go.
行動
Two eleven! Two eleven! We're being held up!
有劫案  我們遇劫
Two-eleven alarm. Armored car.
裝甲車遇劫  已通知了警方
There's the call. Three minutes.
有三分鐘
Clear!
離開
Eighty seconds left!
只剩八十秒
Get back. Get back.
退後
Get back!
Hey, Slick, you see that shit coming out of their ears?
滑頭  他耳朵流血  聽不到的
They can't fucking hear you. Cool it.
別胡來
I got it.
找到了
Got it.
到手
You had to fuck with me.
你要和我過不去
You wanna fuck with me?
Come on! What the fuck are you doing?
快撤  你在做什麼
- What did you do? - I had to, man.
- 你幹了什麼  - 迫不得已  夥計
- Guy was making a move. - Let's go.
- 他作勢要攻擊  - 快走
Dumb motherfucker.
我操你媽
- Step back, please, sir. - I heard them.
- 請退後  先生  - 我聽到他們了
A million six.
一百六十萬
Forty cents on the dollar, 640,000 to you.
每元分四角  你可得六十四萬
Here's a 150 front money.
這是十五萬的預支
Get you the rest in two, three days.
其餘的兩三天後付
Know who owned these?
知道是誰擁有的嗎
Malibu Equity and Investments.
馬莉堡股票及投資公司
Roger Van Zant. Owns banks in the Caymans.
羅傑·宏山  在開曼群島擁有銀行
Runs investment portfolios for offshore drug money. Stuff like that.
替國外毒販洗錢  並負責投資事務
- So? - So you ripped off his bearer bonds.
- 那麼  - 你偷了他的債券
He's got insurance.
他買了保險
That's the point. He collects 100 percent from the insurance.
他可以獲得百分百的保險賠償
He's a player. Maybe he buys his bonds back from us for 60 percent of their value.
也許他向我們購回債券
And make 40 percent on top of the 100 percent.
六折價購回  再賺四成
Sell it back to him instead of going to the street. That's an extra 320,000 to you.
債券賣給他  你可以再得到三十二萬
Try it on him.
試試看
- Kelso called. - About what?
- 祈素來電話  - 關於什麼事
A score he's putting out and wants you to look at.
他找人參與買賣
What do I need his score for? I got my own.
我不需要  我自己有買賣
Says it's clean and low eight figures.
說錢無法追查而且超過千萬元
- 9 a.m. tomorrow. - What happened out there?
- 明天九時  - 那兒發生了什麼事
Don't ask.
別問了
Find the ambulance?
找到救傷車了嗎
- Dumped it four blocks from here. - 22nd Street between Figueroa and Flower.
- 在四條街外遭棄掉  - 在二十二街的花店門口
They torched it. Burned everything. The guns, clothes, everything.
縱火燒掉  槍和衣服化為灰燼
Investigators are still working the scene...
調查員仍在現場工作
They were airborne. Taped the last few seconds...
記者用直升機
...of the black-and-whites doing demolition derby.
拍下幾秒的黑白片
Stolen out of Fresno two weeks ago.
救傷車兩星期前被偷
Yellow pickup truck out of whittier day before yesterday.
黃色車是前天在惠帝爾被偷
You taking this one, lieutenant, or does it stay in Division?
你負責此案  還是由分局調查
This look like gangbangers working the local 7-11 to you?
這一宗是便利店劫案嗎
- Robbery-Homicide's taking it. Yeah. - All yours.
- 搶劫及兇殺組接手調查  - 全歸你了
We got three motorists. All they saw were men with masks. They were distant.
三名司機目擊事發  只看見戴上面具的人
Console TV man over there however, he was closer.
那邊的電視流浪漢距離現場很近
He ID anybody?
他能認出任何人嗎
Well, he was hiding. He heard it mostly.
他躲起來了  聽到大部分對話
Okay. What about them?
他們呢
Right. Now, according to TV man, this guy started mouthing off.
電視漢說這人在胡言亂語
- Smart. - Yeah, somebody called a guard "Slick".
- 很聰明  - 有人把護衛叫作滑頭
- Slick? - Yeah.
- 滑頭  - 是的
Now, this guy... I figure this guy went for that holdout piece, ankle holster, right?
我認為此人  想拿綁在足踝的槍
From here.
由這兒
Bang. Bang. Bang, bang, bang.
開槍
To his side.
子彈由這兒穿出
This guy here has got what appears to be a double-tap entry wound to the sternum.
這人看來好像是胸部中槍
Tattooing around the head wound, scorched bone, close range.
從頭的傷勢看似乎是近距離被殺
Probably executed.
很可能是處決
And it was a million six in bearer bonds, and they ignored the loose cash.
一百六十萬的債券被盜  他們沒拿走現金
Because they had no time, because they were on a clock.
因為他們沒時間  時間緊迫
Which means they knew our response time to a 2-11...
他們知道警方何時會到達
...had our air, immobilized it, entered...
聽警方廣播  把車截停  進入
...escaped in under three minutes.
及在三分鐘內逃走
It's a good spot here. We got good escape routes.
這是好地點  有良好逃走路線
- Two freeways within a quarter of a mile. - Traffic video camera?
- 兩條公路在四分之一英里以內  - 交通錄影呢
Probably disabled. Check it anyway.
可能給弄壞了  但還是查看一下
You recognize the M.O.?
你能認出手法嗎
M.O. is that they're good.
手法  是職業劫匪所為
Once it escalated into a murder-one beef for all of them...
他們殺死兩名警衛  犯了一級謀殺罪
...after they killed the first two guards, they didn't hesitate...
之後便不再遲疑
...popped guard number three because what difference does it make?
殺了第三名  因為橫豎也是犯罪
Why leave a living witness?
為何留下證人呢
Drop of a hat, these guys will rock 'n' roll.
他們會毫不遲疑  心狠手辣
The shape charge.
定向炸藥
The shape charge indicates that they are technically proficient.
顯示劫匪的技術是精通的
Proficient enough to go in on the prowl.
足以使他們在途中下手
So let's start looking for recent high-line burglaries that have mystified us.
我們要找偷值錢東西的劫匪
Run "Slick" as an alias to the FBI.
查滑頭這個綽號
You're gonna get the phone book. Do it anyway.
名單可能很長  但還是要查
Who's moving the bearer bonds?
誰賣出債券
Check the usual fences. You and I will check Cusamano and Torena.
查慣常接贓者 你和我查古和陶
I want you to take Goldstein and Alfaro. Hang in with Forensics.
我要你查高士丹及艾化魯  和鑒證科緊密合作
From the bomb squad, I want the explosive.
向炸彈組查問用的是什麼炸藥
If we're lucky, it's exotic. We can trace the sale.
若是罕見的  便可追查發售來源
Get your hand out of that man's pocket, Rachel.
你別伸手進那人的口袋
Oh, Vince.
噢  雲信
Want some pie?
有誰要吃批餅
Gotta go to the john.
我要上廁所
Look, I had to get it on, man. He was making a move. I had to get it on.
他作勢攻擊  我要先下手為強
Split's in the car. I took out of ours evenly...
他那份在車上  我們的均分了
...to make up for his full end.
以便全數給他
Because I wanna pay off and get rid of this motherfucker right now.
因為我想立即分給他  打發這雜種
Okay.
好的
Hold it!
等一等
Hey.
嘿
- Where's the rest? - We're late.
- 其餘的錢呢  - 時候不早了
Ooh, you look too good to go out. I could just jump you right here.
你打扮得很漂亮  我想在這兒和你做愛
- Where is it? - Uh, squared the bookies, baby.
- 錢呢  - 還給外圍馬的人了
There's more in a couple days, so don't sweat it. We really are late.
幾天後還會有錢  放心吧
Yeah, come on, you gotta be kidding me.
少胡說  你一定是說笑
Honey, it ain't worth the risks you take for 8000.
親愛的  就為了區區八千元值得冒這個險嗎
Like in risk versus reward, baby.
危險和報酬要成正比
Let's go. Get your coat.
走吧  拿上你的外衣
There is no point talking to you. All you are is a child growing older.
無謂再說  你心智還沒成熟
What's that supposed to mean?
什麼意思
It means we're not making forward progress like real grown-up adults, living our lives.
我們不像成年人那樣有進步
I'm married to a gambling junkie who won't listen.
因為我嫁給了一個賭徒
Charlene, get in the fucking car.
上車吧
What am I doing in this rat-bastard situation?
我怎麼可以這樣下去的
You're not! What do you want from me? Leave the bankbook and car keys...
你不用  你離開這裏時
...in the kitchen on your way out. Are we going, or am I going alone?
留下銀行存折和車匙
You could keep that other crap but Dominick would go with me.
你留著吧  我只帶多明一起走
Don't you even think about...
你別妄想
Yeah. Tell me Albert Torena called back.
陶·亞拔覆電話了
- Albert Torena call Vincent? - No.
- 陶·亞拔有給雲信電話嗎  - 沒有
No. Report came in.
沒有  有報告
The explosive was Dynex, linear-shaped charge used in demolition.
炸藥是拆毀用的
You can pick it up with a driver's license in Nevada, Arizona, New Mexico.
可在內華達  亞利桑拿  新墨西哥州買到
- Too common to trace a sale, Vincent. - Oh, that's wonderful.
- 太普通  難以追查來源  - 那太好了
Are you all right?
你沒事吧
What happened? Where you been?
怎麼了  你去了哪兒
Work.
工作
Lauren's dad show up?
羅蘭的父親有來嗎
Didn't call, didn't show. We waited for you till 10:30.
沒來電話  沒出現  我們等你直至十時半
Now, does this guy have any idea what's going on with his kid?
這人知道他女兒是怎樣的嗎
I don't know.
我不知道
Fucking jerk.
該死的混蛋
Well, is she okay?
她沒事吧
She's been in her room all day.
她整天在房內
So no, she's not okay. Neither am I.
她很難過  我亦不開心
Uh, I made dinner for us, four hours ago. Um...
我弄了晚餐  四小時前為我們煮了
Every time I try to maintain a consistent mood between us, you withdraw.
我設法替我們保持一貫的情緒  你退卻了
I got three dead bodies on a sidewalk off Venice Boulevard, Justine.
在威尼斯大道旁邊躺著三名死者  彩鈿
I'm sorry...
對不起
...if the goddamn chicken...
若那可惡的雞
...got overcooked.
給煮過了頭
...seven men in Denmark, to a key defendant here.
丹麥的七個人  是此案的關鍵被告
- Did you find it? - Not yet.
- 你找到了嗎  - 還沒有
There it is.
找到了
It's over here, somewhere.
過了這裏  就在某一處
- Interior design? - It's on the back wall.
- 室內設計呢  - 在後牆那邊
- Coffee, sir? - Please.
- 要咖啡嗎  - 好的
Will you pass the cream?
請把奶遞給我
- Thanks. - What did you get?
- 謝謝  - 你買了什麼
What?
什麼
What are you reading?
你在看什麼書
Book about metals.
關於金屬的書
Stress Fractures in Titanium.
鈦的應力折斷
What kind of work you do?
你幹什麼工作的
Lady, why are you so interested in what I read or what I do?
你為何對我看什麼書幹什麼工作感興趣
I've seen you in the store from time to time.
我在店中看到過你
What store?
什麼店
Hennessey + Ingalls. I work there.
書店  我在那兒工作
Uh...
呃
If you don't wanna talk to me, it's okay. I'm sorry I bothered you.
若你不想交談  好的  抱歉打擾你了
I didn't mean to be rude. I didn't recognize you.
我不想無禮  只是認不出你
I work in metals. I'm a salesman. My name's Neil.
我是營業員  專門推銷金屬的  我叫尼爾
I'm Eady.
我叫伊荻
You like working there?
你喜歡在書店工作
Sure.
是的
I get a discount and there's a whole section of books in my area.
我買書有折扣  亦有我行內的書
What area's that?
是哪一行業
Graphic design.
平面設計
I do, um, letterheads and logotypes at night...
晚上設計信紙及商標
...and the store's a day job till I get enough going.
白天在書店工作直至能藉此謀生
Who do you do that for?
你為誰設計呢
Uh, a restaurant.
餐廳
I did their menus, and, um...
我設計他們的餐牌  以及
...a small, uh, record label.
為小唱片公司設計
CDs. I've done two so far.
鐳射唱片封套  目前已設計了兩張
You go to school for that?
你上學校受訓嗎
Heh, yeah.
是的
- Yeah, I went to Parsons. - Where's that?
- 我念過巴桑學校  - 在哪兒
New York City.
紐約市
How long you been out here?
你在這兒住了多久
About a year.
約一年
You like it?
喜歡這兒嗎
Not really. I'm mostly here for the work.
不算喜歡  我為工作才來這兒
- Live in this neighborhood? - Ah, no...
- 你住在附近嗎  - 不
...I live, um, kind of above Sunset Plaza.
我住在日落廣場上面山上
It's actually kind of... It's a little house that I rent.
租住一所小房子
And it's just kind of run-down, but a beautiful, beautiful view.
頗為破舊  但景觀極佳
What about you?
你呢
- I live up here. - That's very funny.
- 我住在這兒  - 很有趣
So where's your family from originally?
你的家人原本從哪兒來
Um...
嗯
I'm Scotch-Irish.
是蘇格蘭及愛爾蘭裔
They, um, emigrated to Appalachia in the late 1700s.
一七零零年末期移居美國東南部
Where are you from?
你從哪兒來
The Bay Area.
三藩市灣區
Are your folks there?
家人在那兒
Uh, my mother died a long time ago, and my father, I don't know where he is.
母親很久前死了  我父親  我也不知他在哪兒
Got a brother somewhere.
我有個兄弟
You have a tight family. I can tell.
你的家人關係很緊密吧
- Yep. - Right?
- 是的  - 是嗎
You're right.
你說得對
Yeah...
是啊
City of lights.
燈火通明的城市
In Fiji, they have these iridescent algae. They come out once a year in the water.
在菲濟  有一種會發光的海藻  每年浮出水面一次
That's what it looks like out there.
這城市的燈正是如此
You been there?
你到過菲濟
No, I'm going there someday.
沒有  我終有一天會去
Oh, yeah?
是嗎
You travel a lot?
你常旅遊
- Yeah. - Traveling makes you lonely?
- 是的  - 旅遊使你寂寞
I... I'm alone. I am not lonely.
我一個人  可我並不寂寞
You?
你呢
I get lonely.
很寂寞
Albert!
亞拔
- Shit. - Albert.
- 糟了  - 亞拔
Vincent, what you doing coming here, man?
你為何來這兒
You crazy? This ain't Disneyland.
你瘋了嗎
You were supposed to get back to me last night, Albert. Where the fuck you been?
你該回覆我電話的  你去了哪兒
- I couldn't break free, Vincent. You know. - Let's violate his ass right now.
- 我無法脫身  - 我們侵犯他的民權吧
I do for you, you don't do for me, is that it?
我幫你忙  你卻不幫我  是這樣嗎
Vincent, man, I swear, I was out all night, man.
我整晚外出
I'm hitting like one of them flamingo-matador guys.
為你刺探消息
Flamingo? That's got nothing to do with me.
此事和我無關
I was cutting it real smooth. I'm generating leads and shit for you.
我順利為你找到線索
- I'm a dancer, man. You know. - Bullshit.
- 我很棒  - 你胡說
I paged your ass all day. I can't stand paging.
我傳呼你一整天  我討厭這樣做
You're a speed freak, jacking methamphetamine again.
你又再是癮君子  注射毒品
Where is your empathy, brother? It's a substance-abuse problem.
我有濫用藥物的問題  心領吧
Empathy was yesterday.
我昨天對你心領
Today you're wasting my motherfucking time.
你今天卻浪費我時間
- Vincent, man, look... - Did you fall in love?
- 聽著  - 你戀愛了嗎
Come on. Did you fall in love last night and you went off somewhere?
你是否戀愛和到別處去啦
- Vincent... - Just tell me that. I'll settle for it.
- 雲信  - 我會接受這解釋
- I'll buy that. - Vincent.
- 我會信的  - 雲信
Give me all you got!
把消息告訴我
- Vincent... - Give me all you got!
- 雲信  - 把資料對我說
I swear, man, my brother, man. My brother Richard's gonna talk to you.
我發誓  我哥哥裏察會跟你說
I heard "Richard"?
你是說裏察嗎
- He's gonna talk to you. - Richard?
- 他會和你說的  - 裏察
- Richard. - Richard.
- 裏察  - 裏察
- He's gonna meet you, I swear, tonight. - He's not here, is he?
- 他今晚會見你  - 他在這兒
- No, he's gonna meet you tonight. - Tonight? What happened to now?
- 不  他會見你  - 現在不行嗎
I... I... I implored him because I knew you was coming this a.m.
我懇求他  因為我知道你今早會到來
- This is a bunch of bullshit. - No, no, I swear.
- 胡說  - 沒有  我發誓
He said no because he in Phoenix.
他不肯的  因為他在鳳凰城
- Ahh. - But this, man, I swear... I swear, man.
- 啊  - 我發誓
By the time I get to Phoenix,
我到了鳳凰城後
He'll be risin',
他會起程
He'll probably leave a note right on the door
可能留下字條  貼在門上
Tonight's the best I can do for you, man.
我只能令他今晚見你
You know? He'll meet you at BJ's on Alvarado...
今晚在艾華瓦度街BJ夜總會
...at 2 a.m. Be there.
凌晨二時  你去吧
You be there too.
你亦要到
Vincent, I can't be there, man. I got things to do, Vincent.
不行  我有事要辦
- I got things to do, places to be. I got... - Hey, hey, hey.
- 我有事辦  要到別處  - 嘿
Be there.
你要去
Don't waste my motherfucking time!
你別浪費我的時間
What is it?
是什麼買賣
It's a bank.
是銀行
It depos cash on Thursday for distribution to all the other branches...
星期四會存錢以便分發各分行
...to cover Friday payroll checks.
應付星期五支付薪金的支票
So on Thursdays, the command branch has got a full whack.
總行夾萬內星期四總放滿現鈔
- On the prowl or strong? - Strong. Through the front door.
- 在途中下手還是劫銀行  - 由正門進入
How many guys?
有多少人
Four, or three plus a driver. Walk in, knock them over, walk out.
連司機四人  走進銀行  得手便走
And you want a 100,000 advance...
你要先拿十萬
...against a 10-percent cut for that?
事成後分一成
Sounds like an address to a cowboy score. They hit the holdup alarms...
聽似是西部牛仔劫銀行  他們按動警鐘
...I gotta get out before the cops show. What is that?
我得在之前離去
They hit three holdup alarm systems.
他們可按動三個遇劫警鐘
Two telco and a cellular.
兩個一般警鐘和一個蜂窩式的
See, but the signals aren't going anywhere because...
但訊號無法傳送出去  因為
See, the night before, you cut in and trick out the alarm-system computer...
之前一晚  你潛進銀行  破壞警報系統的電腦
...to turn itself and the video recorders off 20 minutes before you walk in the door.
使電腦及錄影裝置在你下手前二十分鐘關掉
Architectural, electrical-engineering plans?
你有建築及電子藍圖嗎
I got all that. Schematics, got the boards already built. They go straight into the CPU.
我有  我建造電腦板  直駁中央處理器
What's the estimate?
估計可有多少錢
12.1, 12.2 million.
一千兩百一十萬到一千兩百二十萬
You're on.
我會參加
Congratulations.
恭喜
And to give you a little idea of where my estimates come from, this is a printout...
我告訴你如何估計會有這筆錢
Nobody knew the merch was yours.
沒人知道貨是你的
Be that as it may, my way you get 100 percent from the insurance company...
我讓你得保險全數
...and take the bonds from us at 60 cents on the dollar...
賠償以六成價  把債券回購
...and make yourself another 40 percent.
你可多賺四成
Your operation doesn't skip a beat. Everybody makes out.
行動全無損失  我們均可賺大錢
Sure, you got a deal.
我同意
Good, because there's no percentage if everyone gets their underwear in a twist.
好  若大家不喜歡便沒得益
Yeah, so you have your man call me and we'll set the meet.
要你的人給我電話  安排會面
Yeah, okay.
行啊  可以
Nice talking to you.
高興和你通電話
You gonna deal with these guys?
你要和他們交易嗎
So word's out on the street it's okay to steal my stuff.
江湖上可接受我偷自己的東西嗎
I'm gonna kill the sons of bitches.
我會殺了這班渾蛋
Have Harry bring me the spreadsheets for Canary Islands' offshore.
命哈利給我加那利群島的試算紙
That's not really an estimate. Those are exact figures.
這些不是估計  是實在數字
I have a printout of the, uh, cash flow of the bank for the past two months.
我印出銀行過去兩月的現金帳
- How'd you get this information? - Just comes to you.
- 資料怎麼得來的  - 送上門的
This stuff just flies through the air.
資料府拾皆是
They send information out and it's beamed out all over the place.
到處傳送  只需加以掌握便行
All you have to do is know how to grab it. See, I know how to grab it.
我懂得掌握
Um... Okay, here we go. Thirteen-point-nine million.
這是我們要的  一千三百九十萬
- I bought it. - Good.
- 我同意了  - 好啊
What did I tell you?
我沒說錯吧
Here.
拿著
We're on. Call Van Zant, collect the money.
同意了  聯絡宏山  準備收錢吧
- How is he? - He's a businessman.
- 他怎麼樣  - 他是生意人
Okay.
好吧
- Avocado. - Avocado.
- 鱷梨  - 鱷梨
- Hello? - Yeah, hello.
- 喂  - 是我
Chris is at my place.
基斯在我家中
- What's wrong? - Husband-and-wife stuff.
- 怎麼了  - 夫妻的爭吵
I'll let him sleep it off here.
我讓他睡醒再算
What happened to you?
你怎麼了
- When you gonna get some furniture? - When I get around to it.
- 你何時買傢俱  - 我有時間便買
Charlene's gonna leave me.
莎蓮要離開我
Why?
為什麼
Not enough steaks in the freezer.
我無好好供養她
With everything we've been doing?
我們做買賣還不夠錢嗎
Vegas and the Super Bowl cleaned me out.
賭場及賭球賽使我身無分文
- When you gonna get an old lady? - When I get around to it.
- 你何時會結婚  - 有時間再算
You got something else on the side?
你有外遇嗎
Nothing regular.
沒固定的
She got something else on the side?
她有外遇嗎
- No. - You sure?
- 沒有  - 你肯定嗎
Yeah, I'm sure.
肯定
I don't know what you're doing.
我不知你做什麼
Remember Jimmy MacAwain on the yard used to say:
如占美說
You wanna be making moves on the street?
你想當罪犯嗎
Have no attachments. Allow nothing to be in your life...
要無牽掛  生活中不能有任何牽掛
...that you cannot walk out on in 30 seconds flat...
風聲緊時便可拋下一切
...if you spot the heat around the corner.
一走了之
Remember that?
記得嗎
For me, the sun rises and sets with her, man.
她是我一生中最重要的
Yeah?
是嗎
Yeah.
是的
Okay.
好吧
Today we take delivery of cash from Van Zant...
我們從宏山那兒拿到錢
...then I drop our deposit on Kelso for this bank.
然後為劫銀行的事存錢給祈素
Bank? What bank?
什麼銀行
What about the platinum thing? It's ready to fall.
這白金的事如何  快成事了
That goes too, then the bank.
那亦會進行  然後再劫銀行
- You want some breakfast? - Yeah.
- 要吃早餐嗎  - 好啊
Are you okay?
你沒事吧
Yeah, sugar.
沒事
Yeah.
耶
- For real. - Okay.
- 是真的  - 好吧
Gonna do good.
我會好好的做
I'll see you later.
再見
You Solenko? I'm Don Breedan.
你是索倫戈嗎  我是當·畢頓
Grierson, my parole officer, told me to come by here and see if you had a job for me.
假釋官告訴我  你會有工作給我
- You're familiar with this kind of operation? - Yeah, man. I'm a great grill man.
- 你對工作嫻熟嗎  - 我燒烤很出色的
Good. Good for you. Here, you'll mop the toilets, hit the dishwasher...
好  你洗抹廁所  洗碗碟
...bus tables and empty the garbage too.
收拾桌子
Give me a hard time, I'll report you loaded, drunk or stealing.
你若煩我  我就舉報你藏毒酗酒或偷竊
And I will violate you back so fast your head will spin.
很快舉報你違反假釋條例
Twenty-five percent of your take-home kicks back to me.
你給我薪金的百分之二十五作為回佣
Rules of the game. Call Grierson, check it out.
是規矩  問假釋官吧
Change in the back.
後面更衣
Well, what are you waiting for?
你還等什麼
Malibu Equity and Investments.
馬莉堡股票及投資
- Yeah, Roger Van Zant. - Please hold.
- 羅傑·宏山  - 請稍等
Yeah, this is Roger Van Zant.
我是羅傑·宏山
I'm supposed to collect something.
我該有一些東西的
Give me your number, and somebody will call you right back from a different line.
把你的號碼告訴我  會有人給你回覆電話
818-133-6089.
818-133-6089
Yep.
喂
I got a package for you.
我有個包裹給你
There's a drive-in on Centinela. 02:30 tomorrow.
明午二時半露天影院見
Okay, just send one man, alone.
只派一人單獨前來
- Who was that guy? - Nobody.
- 那人是誰  - 無名小卒
Who the...? Who...? Who was that guy?
那人是誰
- He's nobody. - I gotta know who he is. Who is he?
- 無名小卒  - 我要知道他是誰
- He's nobody, Neil. - Listen, you...
- 他是無名小卒  - 聽著
He's a legit liquor wholesaler from Las Vegas.
他是賭城合法酒類營業員
- Alan Marciano. - Chris is gonna straighten it up with you.
- 馬·亞倫  - 基斯會與你和解
- It's too late. I'm sick of it. I'm sick of it! - Shut up!
- 太遲了  我討厭他  - 閉嘴
Here's the deal. You'll give Chris one last shot.
你再給基斯一次機會
After that, he fucks up, then I will finance setting you up myself...
若他再犯錯  我會資助你找地方住
...on my own, anywhere you want.
住哪裏都行
Dominick will go with you. And my word counts.
多明也會跟著你  我言出必行
But right now, you will give him the chance.
但現在  你得再給他一次機會
Clean up. Go home.
清洗一下  回家去
Give me all your money.
交出你的錢
One day you gonna get smoked with that shit.
你會因此而沒命的
Ain't gonna be you, fool.
殺我的不會是你
- He's coming in alone. Send him through. - Yeah, got it.
他一個人來
Vincent, hey, man.
雲信
Vincent. This is my brother, Richard. Richard, Vincent.
這是我哥哥裏察  雲信
- Richard. - Yo, it's all right.
- 裏察  - 沒關係
What have you got for me?
你有何消息告訴我
Before we even get into that...
談正題前
...there's this crew ripping rides all along the beach areas, all right?
沙灘附近有人偷車
Now, the back of a trim shop on Irvine...
在汽車裝飾店後
...if somebody was to pay a little visit this weekend...
若週末有人前去那兒
...they might find two Turbos and a 911 Slope.
會找到一輛名貴跑車
You're looking to rid yourself of your competition.
你參加賽車嗎
Eh, I'm a good citizen.
我是個好市民
I'm Donald Duck. So you got something to tell me or what?
我才不信  你有事要告訴我
Check this out, coz.
你聽著  朋友
How do I know if I tell you what you need to know...
我怎知若我說出你所想知的事
...you're gonna do what the fuck I need to get done?
你會做我所想做的事
Richard, man, Hanna is straight up, man. We do business all the time.
裏察  韓很可靠的
I ain't your coz, you rat motherfucker.
雜種  我不是你的朋友
And you know because I say so after I hear what the fuck you gotta tell me.
你知道我說得出做得到  但我要先聽你有什麼話要說
Look here, man. You understand what I'm saying?
我操  明白嗎
I can get killed for telling you this shit.
我說出來會沒命的
Or you're gonna get killed walking your doggie.
你溜狗時亦會沒命
All right.
好吧
There's this cat I was locked up with in Folsom.
我和這人在獄中相識
Did a couple, two, three years. He got out and I ran into him.
服刑兩三年  他出獄後我碰上他
And so?
那又怎樣
He's a big fiend for action.
他是坐言起行的人
Now, if he'd have said nothing, I'd have thought nothing...
若他不說  我便不會去想  可是
...but he goes on and on, running down to me how he ain't been doing nothing...
他不斷的對我說他什麼也沒做
...and nothing's been going on, and all this bullshit.
而且也沒事發生  等等等等
So right then and there I know this cat's got something going down.
那時我便知道  這人參與了不法行為
Pretty fucking great.
而且是大案
Albert, what's wrong with you?
亞拔  你怎麼回事
You drag me here, waste my time like this.
你要我來這裏  浪費我的時間
You saw a guy on the street who's an ex-con?
你見過坐過牢的人
- That's right. - Well, I am over-fucking-whelmed.
- 是的  - 那麼我很喜出望外
What do you want for that, a Junior G-man badge?
你想為此拿警章嗎
You gonna make the call on them Porsches or what?
你會查跑車的事嗎
Is he kidding me?
他是說笑嗎
I'm telling you, this Slick is no joke.
我告訴你  滑頭從不說笑
You know what I'm saying?
他為人緊張
- Say what? Say what? - What?
- 你說什麼  - 什麼
- You said, "Slick". What does that mean? - Slick. That's what he calls people, "Slick".
- 滑頭  那是什麼意思  - 他常叫別人為滑頭
And tell me about him.
把他的事告訴我
About 6 feet tall, lot of jailhouse tats.
他約六英尺高  有許多監獄的紋身
Got a big-ass peacock right here.
這兒刺有一頭大孔雀
What's his name?
他叫什麼名字
Cheritto.
姓查
Michael Cheritto.
查·米高
33 busts since 1976.
自一九七六年起被捕三十三次
Eleven for armed robbery, three convictions.
十一次持械行劫  三次給定罪
Two out of a three-to-five-year beef in Attica. Three years in Marion.
判刑三至五年  在紐約服刑兩年
Five years in Folsom off a knock-back to involuntary manslaughter.
中西部服刑三年  因誤殺罪在霍森監獄服刑五年
- Jacket's 2 inches thick. - Okay.
- 他的案底達兩英吋厚  - 很好
- Who do I have there now? - Drucker and me, boss. And Schwartz.
- 現在還有誰有聽  -  澤加和我  以及舒華茲
Tell SIS I want full surveillance.
通知特別調查科
That's 24 hours. Round the clock, day and night.
我要二十四小時監視他
We never close. Open seven days a week. Bug the car, the house, the work.
不斷監視跟蹤他  監聽他的汽車和房子
When he moves or sits, like in a restaurant...
一舉一動
...I want pictures of who he moves and sits with.
和誰人一起也拍照
Then run makes on them. They got jackets, I wanna see who they move and sit with.
調查他們  若有案底便跟蹤他們
I want it up and running by tomorrow night.
我要明天便執行
- Put your hands where I can see them. - What?
- 把手放在我看得到的地方  - 什麼
- Put your hands where I can see them. - All right.
- 把手放在我看得到的地方  - 好的
I tell you what to do, I tell you how to do it.
我會告訴你做什麼  以及怎樣去做
Now, with your right hand only, your right hand only...
現在  只用你的右手  只准右手
...take the package and throw it in here.
把包裹拿出來  扔過來
Fuck. Behind you. On the right.
你右面  後面有人
Yeah, Roger Van Zant?
羅傑·宏山
- Yeah, who's this? - You know who this is.
- 你是誰  - 你知道我是誰
Yes, I do. Yes, I do.
我知道
I sent a guy to deliver the package. He didn't call. Is everything right?
我派人送包裹  他沒來電話  一切妥當吧
Tell you what, forget the money.
我告訴你  忘記那筆錢
- What? - Forget the money.
- 什麼  - 忘記那筆錢
Wh...
呃
It's a lot of money. What are you doing? What do you mean, forget the money?
數目不少  你究竟想做什麼  忘記那筆錢是什麼意思
What am I doing? I'm talking to an empty telephone...
我在做什麼  我在對著話筒自說自話
I don't understand.
我不明白
...because there is a dead man on the other end of this fucking line.
因為電話的另一端是個死人
Oh, my.
天吶
- Do you like it? - Look at my ring.
- 你喜歡嗎  - 看我的戒指
Wow.
真漂亮
Did you know about this? It's so beautiful.
你知道的嗎
You are insane.
你瘋了
Do you like it?
喜歡嗎
- It's beautiful. - Yeah, it's pretty good.
- 很漂亮  - 是啊  很漂亮
- Just don't ask him where he got it. - Yeah, that's right.
- 別問他哪兒得來的  - 對  別問
What do you wanna be when you grow up, honey?
你長大後想做什麼  寶貝
I don't know.
我不知道
She doesn't know. Just like me. I don't know either.
她不知道  像我一樣  我亦不知道
Hello?
你好
Hi, it's me.
嗨  是我
Hey. I was wondering if you'd call.
我在想你是否會來電話
I've been busy. Can I see you?
我很忙  我能見你嗎
I was afraid that was just the one night, you know?
我害怕那只是一夜情
No, not for me, it wasn't.
對我來說不是
Yeah, me neither.
我也不是
Can I fall by?
我能來嗎
- Yeah. - Okay, I'll see you in a little bit.
- 可以  - 好的  一會兒見
Thank you.
謝謝
Good night.
晚安
Goddamn convention.
可惡的會議
- Which one's Slick? - The wide one.
- 哪一個是滑頭  - 魁梧的那個
Got two transmitters.
有兩個監視器
One's in the wheel well, backup's in the firewall.
分別在防火板及輪內
Okay, get ready.
是我們的車
- Did you say good night to Neil? - Good night.
- 跟尼爾道別了嗎  - 晚安
One with the blond hair is Chris Shiherlis. SIS has got a revolving tail...
金髮的是施基斯  特別調查組已派人跟蹤他
...and hung a wire on the house phone.
並監聽了他家的座機
Cheritto's cruised the precious-metals depository three times.
查把車三次駛過貴重金屬庫
Platinum, silver, and some bullion.
白金銀和一些金條
Sammy and I think that's gonna be their next score.
森美和我認為是他們下一目標
Who's the loner?
那獨行者是誰
First time we're seeing him. We're not on him yet.
我們第一次見他  還沒開始跟蹤他
Well, get on it.
立即開始吧
Okay.
好的
When these guys walk out the door of whatever score they're gonna take next...
他們下次做案得手走出大門時
...they're gonna have the surprise of a lifetime.
一定會大感驚愕
Hey, baby. Time to go.
我要走了
I showed you a good time, didn't I?
我令你很開心吧
Oh, yeah.
是啊
You fly. You cool.
你很棒  你不錯
You're lying to me. I can always tell when people lie to me.
你騙我  我看得出別人騙我
Mm, I ain't lying. You a hot dog.
我沒說謊  你很勇猛
A regular rodeo rider.
是出色的騎士
And this was the monster fuck of my young life.
是我試過最精彩的性行為
Now I got to get my ass street side, sugar.
我現在得回到街上去
You don't have a truth-telling style.
你沒有老實的作風
- What are you talking about? - You don't know what this is.
- 你說什麼  - 你不知道是什麼回事
The Grim Reaper's visiting with you.
是死神來探望你
Where you been?
你去了哪兒
SHU at Pelican Bay.
塘鵝彎的特別收容所
New Folsom, B-wing.
以及霍森監獄B座
I am a cowboy looking for anything heavy.
我是一個想做大買賣的人
Billy Ricketts said come see you.
比利說來找你
That is why I am here.
因此我到來
Why don't you...?
你為何不
Why don't you call this guy?
你為何不打電話給這人
This guy's always putting guys on.
他經常招人入伙
Thank you, brother.
謝謝  兄弟
- I'll buy you a drink? - Buy me a drink.
- 我要請你喝酒嗎  - 請我喝酒
- What's so funny? - Nothing.
- 笑什麼  - 沒什麼
- It's really dumb. - Something smells negligent.
- 這傢伙  真夠傻的  - 你在責備我嗎
You two are perfect for each other. How did you meet?
你們天生一對
I knew this guy in, uh, grade school.
我念小學時認識一人
He was named Raoul, uh... Whatever.
他叫羅爾  什麼的
Anyway, the guy could take his fingers and fold them over, one over the other.
他可以把手指彼此屈折起來
Then he'd turn his eyelids inside out...
他可以把眼瞼向外翻
I can't keep my hands off you, and that's the truth.
我禁不住對你上下其手  是真的
That's what's so wonderful about you, in that bestial sort of way.
你吸引人的地方在於你那獸性的方式
Woman.
女人
This better be earth-shattering.
這最好是轟動的大事
That's what she tells us. To Raoul.
為羅爾乾杯
- Raoul. - To Raoul.
- 羅爾  - 敬羅爾
Yeah, Vincent Hanna.
我是韓·雲信
Here's how we found her.
發現她時是這樣的
- How old? - Sixteen, seventeen.
- 她有多大  - 十六七歲
Been here about six hours.
在此約六小時
How'd she die, Rachel?
她怎麼死的
Beat her head in, same as the others. Cerebral hematoma.
頭部遭受重擊  大腦血腫
Who's that?
那是誰
- Mother and siblings, I guess. - What the hell they doing here?
- 我猜是死者母親及兄弟  - 他們為何到來
Because it's fucked up. Somebody inside knew the girl and called the family.
酒店內有人認識死者  就通知了家人
Okay, let's go.
讓我看看
That's nice.
不錯
When I run a DNA check on the semen, my intuition says it's coming up the same guy.
直覺告訴我  化驗精液是同一人
So it's a series, and ending up in your court.
是連環謀殺案  要由你著手調查
- Sheriff's Homicide getting anywhere? - Not yet.
- 警長有頭緒嗎  - 還沒有
- Get her. - Get off me. Get off me.
- 攔住她  - 放開我
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
噢
- Oh, my God. - Hold it, hold it.
- 天啊  - 冷靜
- Where is she? - Easy, easy, easy.
- 她在哪兒  - 冷靜
Please. Please, come on.
別這樣
- It's okay. It's okay. - Who did this?
- 沒事的  - 誰幹的
Where's my baby? Where is she?
我的女兒呢  她在哪兒
I need to know what happened.
我要知道是什麼回事
I guess the Earth shattered.
我猜是很轟動吧
So why didn't you let Bosko take you home?
你為何不讓博高送你回家
I didn't wanna ruin their night too. What was it?
我不想掃他們的興  有什麼事
You don't wanna know.
你不想知道的
I'd like to know what's behind that grim look.
我想知道你為何扳起臉孔
I don't do that. You know it. Let's go. Come on.
我不能透露  你是知道的
You never told me I'd be excluded.
你從沒告訴我  我會摒諸事外
I told you when we hooked up, baby, that you were gonna have to share me...
我告訴你  我們在一起時  你要和我分享
...with all the bad people and all the ugly events on this planet.
世上所有的醜行及醜惡的人
And I bought into that sharing because I love you.
我同意接受分享  因為我愛你
I love you fat, bald, money, no money, driving a bus. I don't care.
即使你發胖  禿頭  沒錢  我仍會愛你
But you have got to be present like a normal guy some of the time.
但你一定要存在
That's sharing. This is not sharing, this is leftovers.
那是分享  這不是分享  是殘餘的
Oh, I see. What I should do is come home and say:
明白了  我該回家  然後我該說
Hi, honey, guess what? I walked into this house today...
寶貝兒  你知道嗎  我今天走進一所房子
...where this junkie asshole just fried his baby in a microwave...
這癮君子用微波爐煮熟了孩子
...because it was crying too loud, so let me share that with you.
就因為他的哭聲太吵鬧  我和你分享吧
Come on, let's share that, and in sharing it...
讓我們分享此事  而在分享時
...we'll somehow cathartically dispel all that heinous shit, right?
我們會宣洩一切可怕的事件  對嗎
Wrong. You know why?
錯  你知道為什麼嗎
Because you prefer the normal routine.
你喜歡正常的做法
We fuck, then you lose the power of speech.
我們做愛  你不說話
Because I gotta hold on to my angst.
我得保持我的痛苦
I preserve it, because I need it. It keeps me sharp, on the edge.
我保存它  因為我需要藉此提高警覺
Where I gotta be.
我要這樣做
You don't live with me.
你不是和我同住
You live among the remains of dead people.
你和死者的殘骸同住
You read the terrain.
你篩選碎片  在地勢找線索
You search for signs of passing...
你找尋死亡的跡象
...for the scent of your prey...
找獵物的氣味
...and then you hunt them down.
然後追捕他們
That's the only thing you're committed to.
這是你唯一投入的事
The rest is the mess you leave as you pass through.
其餘的是你留下的爛攤子
What I don't understand is why I can't cut loose of you.
我不明白為何不能離開你
Hey. Miss Lillian.
嘿  莉莉安
Let's go, baby.
走吧  寶貝
I met the manager. Is that the boss?
我見過經理  那是老闆嗎
I did time for what that motherfucker does every day.
我為他每天所做的事而坐牢
Baby, can you just handle it till we find you something new?
你可忍受直至找到新工作嗎
Can you do that?
你可以嗎
Ain't a hard time been invented that I cannot handle.
更難忍受的我亦捱過
What you hanging with me for, Lillian?
你為何和我在一起  莉莉安
Because I'm proud of you.
因為你令我感驕傲
You're proud of me?
你以我為榮嗎
What the hell you proud of me for?
為什麼
Come on home.
回家吧
- What were you doing there? - I was skiing.
- 你在哪兒做什麼  - 我滑雪
I was trying to ski.
我想滑雪
That's what people do there. You go skiing...
那兒的人會這樣做  去滑雪
...and you meet people.
可結識別人
You try to have a good time.
你想開心一下
- Did you have a good time? - No.
- 你開心嗎  - 不
Why not?
為什麼
I'm not good at meeting people.
我不擅交際
You met me.
你認識了我
Well, that happened without my thinking about it.
我沒仔細想  事情便發生了
Which is why, probably.
可能是因為這樣
No, it's because you were fine.
不  是因為你是個好女人
Eady.
伊荻
Take off with me for a while.
和我到外地去
- Where? - New Zealand.
- 去哪兒  - 新西蘭
When?
何時
I have to go separate, but you could meet me there.
我不能和你同去  但你可以在那兒與我會和
But my job, my...
但我的工作
I got money. You don't need money. You could set up a studio, do work there.
我有錢  你不用工作  你可以在那兒開設計公司
- I don't know. - What's there to know?
- 我不知道  - 還要知道什麼
Are you married?
你結婚了嗎
- What? - You come and go...
- 什麼  - 你來了又走了
The last thing I am is married.
我才沒有結婚
I'm a needle starting at zero going the other way, a double blank.
我的生活正在走下坡
Then, all of a sudden...
可是  突然
...someone like you comes along.
出現了你這樣的人
- You don't know me, Neil. - I know enough.
- 你不瞭解我  - 足夠瞭解了
Come with me.
跟我走
What's wrong, baby?
有何不妥
Nothing's wrong. Everything's right. Will you go?
沒什麼  一切妥當  你會去嗎
Yeah.
會
Good.
好
- Hey, sweetie. - Hi.
- 嘿  親愛的  - 嗨
What happened? You forget your mom was picking you up?
你忘記媽媽會接你嗎
No.
不是
So, what's going on?
怎麼回事
I felt like being alone.
我想獨自一人待著
Okay. Come on, I'll drive you home.
好吧  上車  我送你回家
- Hey, Mike. - Hey, Lauren.
- 嘿  麥克  - 嘿  羅蘭
What's happening?
有何動靜
Lieutenant. Sir.
長官
Captain Jackson wants to know what's going on.
傑克遜警長想知道有何動靜
Nothing's going on. Stay off the air.
沒動靜  不要用無線電
Jackson's a...
傑克遜
Technique.
好技術
Open sesame. Right there.
芝麻開門
There he goes.
就是他
- We walk. - I'm right there.
- 我們走吧  - 我快完事了
We walk! Now! Come on.
我們撤  即刻  快點
He's heard it.
他聽到了
Heads up.
他們來了
- One's coming out. - Hold it, captain.
- 有一個出來了  - 等一等  隊長
- Vincent, he's not carrying anything. - Yeah, I see.
- 雲信  他沒帶走任何東西  - 是的  我看見了
- Here we go. - Not till my boss says so.
- 行動  - 得讓我上司批准
Vincent, both of them are not carrying anything.
雲信  他們沒拿東西
- Okay, let them go. - What do you mean?
- 讓他們走  - 什麼意思
We can take them...
我們可以拘捕他們
What are you gonna take them on? Breaking and entry?
控以何罪  非法闖入嗎
They didn't steal anything. Don't you get it?
他們沒偷東西  明白嗎
It gets knocked back to some misdemeanor...
行為不檢
...they do six months and they're out. No fucking way.
他們坐牢半年便出獄  不行
I'm not taking the heat from my boss. They're not walking.
我可不想接受批評  他們不能走
That's exactly what they're gonna do. They're gonna walk. This is my operation.
他們會走  今次行動由我指揮
I have tactical command that supersedes your rank.
我的戰略指揮凌駕你的職級
They will walk away and you will let them. Fuck.
他們會離去  你會讓他們走
Back to work.
繼續工作
L.A.P.D. Gee, what? Where the fuck did this heat come from?
洛城警方  密探  警方從何而來
Maybe it's the score they were onto.
他們或許知道那兒會被劫
The place, not us. Because it's been hit a couple of times, you know.
但不知道是我們  因為那兒以前曾遇劫
Assume they got our phones, assume they got our houses...
假設他們知道我們的電話  住所
...assume they got us right here, right now as we sit.
知道我們在此集會
Everything. Assume it all.
假設他們知道一切
How we gonna buy the bank package from Kelso?
我們如何付劫銀行的上期
- I'll front that. That's not a problem. - What happens to Van Zant?
- 我先墊付吧  - 宏山呢
With the heat we got, do you wanna play World War II in the streets with Van Zant?
警方現在正追查我們  你想和他開戰嗎
No, I want my 750. And he gets a pass?
不  我想拿七十五萬
I got more motivation to whack Van Zant than either of you. He is a fucking luxury.
我比你更想殺了宏山  他太放肆了
Our problem is, take the bank or split right now?
問題是  我們劫銀行  還是離去
Do not go home, do not pack, nothing.
不要回家收拾東西
Thirty seconds flat from now, we are gone on our separate ways.
三十秒後我們會各走各路
That's it.
就這樣
Chris.
基斯
The bank is worth the risk.
值得冒險劫銀行
I need it, brother.
我需要錢
We should stay and take it down. That's where I come out.
我認為我們該留下來劫銀行
I roll with you, Neil. Whatever. Whatever.
你做什麼我亦跟隨
No, not on this one, Michael. On this one, you're on your own.
但今次不行  米高  你要自行決定
You figure this is the best thing to do?
這是最好的做法嗎
This is the best thing to do?
是最好的做法嗎
I got plans. I'm going away after. So for me the reward is maybe worth the stretch.
事後我有打算  值得為這筆錢坐牢
But Elaine takes good care of you. You got plenty put away.
但綺玲很照顧你  你有許多錢
You got T-bonds, real estate.
你有物業
If I were you, I would be smart. I would cut loose of this.
若我是你  便不參與今次行動
Well, you know, for me, the action is the juice.
對我來說  行動使生活更刺激
I'm in.
我參加
You too?
你呢
Yeah, sure.
我會
Let's go.
動手吧
Fuck them, let's do it.
去他們的  行動吧
All right, let's go. We got a lot of work to do.
那好  我們有許多事要做
- You can't go in there. - Watch this.
- 你們不能進去  - 查查這個
- Excuse me. That... - Tim, I gotta call you back.
- 抱歉  等等  - 提姆  我回頭再給你打電話
You have to have an appointment.
你得提前預約
- Can I help you? - Are you Alan Marciano?
- 我能幫助你嗎  - 你是馬·亞倫嗎
- Yeah, and who the fuck are you? - Who am I?
- 是我  你他媽是誰  - 我是誰
- Hey. Hey. - Lieutenant Vincent Hanna, L.A.P.D.
- 嘿  - 洛城警局的韓·雲信探長
L.A.? This is Las Vegas. You don't even have jurisdiction here.
這裏是賭城拉斯維加斯  不在你的管轄範圍
Hey. Hey, I don't know who the fuck you guys think you're pushing around...
你知道在惹惱誰嗎
- ...but I know people here, okay? - Las Vegas P.D. takes you into custody.
- 我認識這兒的大人物  - 我可以讓賭城警方拘押你
You are extradited to Newark on a New Jersey warrant...
你會因從北卡羅來納走私香煙
...for smuggling cigarettes up from North Carolina three years ago...
而被引渡回紐華克
...or you go to work for us.
或是你可和我們合作
Cut and dried.
簡單明快
- That is it. - Oh, shit.
- 就是這樣  - 媽的
Charlene Shiherlis.
施·莎蓮
- Who? - Who?
- 誰  - 誰
Who? What are you, a fucking owl?
誰  你是貓頭鷹嗎
The lady you been talking dirty to on the telephone every day the last week.
和你在電話中淫聲浪語的女子
Yeah, you know what? You can't tie me to her.
你不能把她和我扯上了
Who needs to? Your ass is on a plane back to New Jersey, jack off.
你肯定會回去新澤西的  笨蛋
Oh, man, I just... Why did I get mixed up with that bitch?
我為何會勾搭上那個婊子呢
Because she got a great ass!
因為她的屁股很誘人
And you got your head all the way up it.
你不知自己在做什麼
Jesus.
天啊
When I think of asses, a woman's ass...
我很兇  是嗎  當我想起屁股  女人的屁股
...something comes out of me.
便想起一些東西
- So? - So no big thing.
- 那麼  - 不要你說太多
All I want is her husband and his whole fucking crew.
我只想知道她丈夫和他那夥人
Now, you're gonna work with Sergeant Drucker here.
你會和澤加合作
San Clemente Road and Hermosa.
聖金文路和赫摩撒街
That's where we cut through the fence. That's the access.
我們在那兒穿過欄柵
Right.
對
The security systems around here are a joke.
保安系統不堪一擊
St. Vincent Thomas Bridge, that's Escape Route Number 1.
逃走路線一是聖雲遜湯瑪士橋
Number 2, over here, Anaheim to the 110.
路線二  是安納咸公路往一一零號公路
- Good. - Okay?
- 好  - 好嗎
- Yeah. That's fine. - Got it? Good. Let's go.
- 很好  - 明白嗎  好的  走吧
They were looking back...
他們回頭望向
...in this direction.
這方向
A container facility?
貨櫃設施
- For a cartage theft? - Too visible. Too lowball for them.
- 什麼  - 太明顯了  對他們來說得益太少了
Next door's an oil refinery, over there's a scrap yard.
有煉油廠和廢車場
Refinery only pays by check. No cash around. Same for the scrap yard.
煉油廠發薪用支票  沒有現金  廢車場亦一樣
Maybe they're stealing hubcaps.
也許他們要偷車輪蓋
A refinery and a scrap yard.
煉油廠和廢車場
- What the hell is going on? - That's what we're trying to figure out.
- 是什麼回事  - 我們正想知道
We thought we had it.
我們以為很清楚
Thought we had it.
這下倒糊塗了
I got an idea of what they were looking at.
我知道他們在看些什麼
- You wanna know what they're looking at? - What?
- 你們想知道嗎  - 是什麼
I mean, is this guy something, or is he something?
這人真了不起  他真行
This crew is good.
這夥人很棒
You know what they were looking at?
你們想知道嗎
What?
是什麼
Us.
是我們
The L.A.P.D.
洛城警局
The police department.
是警局
We just got made.
我們給人認出了
Yeah.
是的
Okay.
好的
Okay, motherfucker!
好吧  雜種
Kelso come through?
祈素交出來了嗎
Yeah, you can build a bank with these.
交出來了  藍圖很詳盡
Name is Hanna. First name Vincent.
那人姓韓  名雲信
I smeared this sergeant in Vice five yards. Hanna's all over you.
我用五百元賄賂這警員  韓監視你一舉一動
He's on all the work cars. Michael's house, Shiherlis'.
監視所有的車  米高及施的家
Not yours, they've been losing you at night.
沒監視你  不知你晚上在哪兒
Hanna's a hot dog. Graduate school. Marine Corps.
他很積極  他畢業後加入陸戰隊
Lieutenant, Robbery-Homicide, Major Crime Unit.
是劫案及兇殺組探長
He's taken down some heavy crews. Blew away Frankie Yonder in Chicago.
拘捕過不少人  在芝加哥殺了法蘭
And he was a fucking maniac.
法蘭是個狂人
He was working Narcotics before that. Had some problems, divorced twice.
他之前在毒品科工作  離婚兩次
Current wife's Justine. He's why the extra heat.
目前的太太叫彩鈿  是他鼓動嚴密監視的
The Vice sergeant...
罪案科警官
...says Hanna likes you.
說韓喜歡你
Thinks you're some kind of star. You do this sharp, you do that sharp.
認為你是明星  行事很有技巧
Look how sharp this guy is to figure that.
他能想到這樣看他有多聰明
Funny as a heart attack, man. Three marriages.
他像心臟病般好笑  三次婚姻
What the fuck do you think that means? He likes staying home?
你認為他喜歡待在家嗎
Means the man is one of those guys out there...
他是那種
...prowling around all night, dedicated.
整晚工作的人  很投入
With this guy and this much heat, you should pass.
有他和警方監視  取消劫銀行吧
It's worth the stretch.
值得冒險一試
This guy can hit and miss. You can't miss once.
這人是否能抓住罪犯都無所謂  可你輸不起
You sure?
你肯定嗎
I'm sure.
肯定
Let's go to the garage.
我們去車房吧
Justine.
彩鈿
Justine?
Where we going?
我們要去哪兒
- Okay, where are you going? - Out.
- 好吧  你要去哪兒  - 外面
- What are you on? - TAC 9.
- 他們用什麼頻道  - 九號戰術頻道
They're northbound out LAX on the 405. We got four ground units.
他們在四零五號公路  往機場方向北走
This is Vincent Hanna in Air 18. Who have I got?
我是十八號機的韓·雲信  誰和我合作
Hey, Vincent, it's JJ. I'm in Air 40. Richard Glover's with me.
我是四十號機的JJ  高·裏察和我在一起
It's on the 105 eastbound approaching the 110 interchange.
車在一零五號公路  東行接近一一零號公路
- You running a revolving tail? - Yeah, I got two units in front, three behind.
- 是交替追蹤嗎  - 是的  前面有兩輛車  三輛在他後面
Okay, have one of them pick me up at the Vermont on-ramp.
要其中一輛在維蒙街接我
Let's go.
走吧
Am I 100 yards, or what? Am I close or far, or what?
我離他有一百碼嗎   太近還是太遠
Three hundred yards, center lane.
離他三百碼  在中央行車線
How you doing?
你好嗎
What do you say I buy you a cup of coffee?
我請你喝咖啡如何
- Yeah, sure. Let's go. - Follow me.
- 好的  走吧  - 跟著我
Seven years in Folsom.
你在霍森監獄七年
In the hole for three.
單獨囚禁三年
McNeil before that.
之前在麥尼爾監獄
McNeil as tough as they say?
那兒是一如所說的那麼兇殘嗎
You looking to become a penologist?
你想成為監獄學者嗎
You're looking to go back?
你想再坐牢嗎
You know, I chase down some crews guys just looking to fuck up,
我追捕過不少把事情搞砸  只能束手被擒的人
get busted back. That you?
再次送回監獄  你是那種人嗎
You must've worked some dipshit crews.
你拘捕的一定是飯桶笨蛋
I worked all kinds.
我拘捕各式各樣的人
You see me doing thrill-seeking liquor-store holdups...
你幻想我身上有刺青
...with a "Born to Lose" tattoo on my chest?
行劫酒鋪嗎
- No, I do not. - Right.
- 不  我不會的  - 對
I am never going back.
我不會再坐牢
Then don't take down scores.
那麼便別再行劫
I do what I do best, I take scores.
我做擅長做的事  我行劫
You do what you do best, trying to stop guys like me.
你做擅長的事  阻止我
So you never wanted a regular-type life?
你從不想過正常生活
What the fuck is that? Barbecues and ball games?
是怎樣的  燒烤和踢足球嗎
Yeah.
是的
- This regular-type life like your life? - My life? No, my life...
- 你的生活正常嗎  - 我的生活  不  我的生活
No, my life's a disaster zone.
一塌糊塗
I got a stepdaughter so fucked up...
我的繼女情緒深受困擾
...because her real father is this large-type asshole.
因為她的生父是個大混蛋
I got a wife. We're passing each other on the down slope of a marriage...
我有太太  我的婚姻正頻臨破碎邊緣
...my third...
第三次了
...because I spend all my time chasing guys like you around the block.
因為我常花時間追捕你這樣的人
That's my life.
那是我的生活
A guy told me one time:
有人曾對我說
Don't let yourself get attached to anything...
若你感到附近有警方監視
...you are not willing to walk out on in 30 seconds flat...
便不能沾上任何不能脫身的事
...if you feel the heat around the corner.
三十秒內  一走了之
Now, if you're on me, and you gotta move when I move...
你想捉我  我行動時你亦行動
...how do you expect to keep a marriage?
你如何能維持婚姻呢
Well, that's an interesting point.
這說法很有趣
What are you, a monk?
你是僧侶嗎
I have a woman.
我有女伴
What do you tell her?
你怎麼對她說
I tell her I'm a salesman.
我告訴她  我是推銷員
So then, if you spot me coming around that corner...
那麼若你見我從街角走來
...you're just gonna walk out on this woman?
你會離開她嗎
Not say goodbye?
不辭而別
That's the discipline.
那是自律
That's pretty vacant, no?
那很空泛
Yeah, it is what it is.
正是如此
It's that, or we both better go do something else, pal.
不這樣做  我們還是另找職業吧
I don't know how to do anything else.
我不懂做別的
Neither do I.
我也不懂
- I don't much want to either. - Neither do I.
- 我不想做其他事  - 我也不想
You know, I have this recurring dream.
我不斷重複這夢境
I'm sitting at this big banquet table...
我坐在偌大的餐宴席上
...and all the victims of all the murders I ever worked are sitting at this table...
我調查的兇案受害人均出席
...and they're staring at me with these black eyeballs...
他們用黑色的眼珠子瞪望我
...because they got eight-ball hemorrhages from the head wounds.
因為他們頭部中槍而出血
And there they are, these big balloon people...
這些發脹的屍體在那兒
...because I found them two weeks after they'd been under the bed.
因為他們被殺兩周後才在床下發現
The neighbors reported the smell...
鄰居報稱有惡臭
...and there they are, all of them just sitting there.
他們均有出席  所有人坐在那兒
What do they say?
他們說什麼
Nothing.
沒說話
- No talk? - None.
- 沒人說話嗎  - 沒有
Just... They don't have anything to say.
他們無話可說
See, we just look at each other.
我們彼此望著對方
They look at me. And that's it, that's the dream.
他們望著我  就是這樣  夢境是這樣
I have one where I'm drowning.
我夢過自己溺水
And I gotta wake myself up and start breathing, or I'll die in my sleep.
我得弄醒自己  開始呼吸  否則會死
You know what that's about?
你知道這象徵著什麼嗎
Yeah. Having enough time.
知道  有足夠的時間
- Enough time to do what you wanna do? - That's right.
- 有足夠的時間做你想做的事嗎  - 是的
- You doing it now? - No, not yet.
- 你正在這樣做嗎  - 還沒有
You know, we're sitting here...
我們坐在這裏
...you and I, like a couple of regular fellows.
一如常人
You do what you do, and I do what I gotta do.
彼此做有需要的事
And now that we've been face to face...
現在我們見過面
...if I'm there and I gotta put you away, I won't like it.
若我要在案發現場殺你  我會不喜歡的
But I'll tell you...
但是
...if it's between you and some poor bastard...
若在你和
...whose wife you're gonna turn into a widow...
被你殺死的人當中作選擇
...brother, you are going down.
兄弟  沒命的會是你
There's a flip side to that coin.
我有反面的看法
What if you do got me boxed in and I gotta put you down?
若你真的使我走投無路  而我要殺你呢
Because no matter what, you will not get in my way.
因為無論如何  你是無法阻止我的
We've been face to face, yeah...
是的  我們見過面
...but I will not hesitate. Not for a second.
但我會毫不猶疑殺你  一秒也不遲疑
Maybe that's the way it'll be.
也許會這樣
Or who knows?
或是誰曉得呢
Or maybe we'll never see each other again.
也許我們會永遠不再見
They dumped us.
他們擺脫了我們
What?
什麼
- They dumped us. - What do you mean, they dumped us?
- 他們逃脫了  - 什麼意思
Chris slipped his tail.
基斯甩掉了跟蹤他的探員
He doesn't talk about scores with Charlene...
他沒跟莎蓮談及買賣的事
...so there's nothing for me to get from Marciano. I tried.
我無從向馬·亞倫套取資料
- What about Cheritto? - Same.
- 查·米高呢  - 亦一樣
Transponders got put on a bus to San Clemente.
異頻收發器放在公共汽車上
- They dumped all our surveillance? - Yeah, at the same time. 9 p.m.
- 他們擺脫我們所有的監視了嗎  - 是的  同一時間  晚上九時
I had coffee with McCauley half an hour ago!
我半小時前和麥·尼爾喝咖啡
We were on you. Then McCauley drives into LAX...
之後他駛往機場
...where surveillance can't fly over because of flight paths.
我們便無法飛去
His car's still there. He's gone.
他的車仍在那兒  但人走了
Does anybody have any idea where the fuck these people are?
有誰知道他們在哪兒嗎
You hear from him yet?
他有聯絡嗎
Not a thing. And not hearing bothers me more. Where's this guy?
沒有  這令我不安  他在哪兒
This guy here. We put him on. Says he knows McCauley.
這人  我們僱用他  他說認識麥·尼爾
Who are you?
你是誰
Waingro. My name's Waingro.
榮谷  我叫榮谷
I've been living in this office day and night. How well do you know him?
我等他電話  你很熟識他嗎
Oh, we took some major scores together.
我們一起做過不少大買賣
How come I haven't heard from him?
他為何沒找我
Well, he's probably busy right now, but he's real thorough.
他可能忙著  但他行事很徹底
- He ain't gonna forget about you. - Oh, that's reassuring.
- 他不會忘記你的  - 噢  那真令人安心
Well, I got some moves I could make here.
我可在這兒出了力
Probably be a big help to you.
可能對你會很有幫助
You recognize the grill man?
認得那烤肉的人嗎
- No. - Folsom. D-block. Housed with Dobie Rush.
- 不認識  - 霍森監獄  D座的  和杜比同一囚室
- Ain't got my break yet, man. - Cisco and Pancho didn't show.
- 我還沒有小休  - 薜哥和彭曹沒上班
Haul out the garbage. Mop up the back.
扔垃圾  到餐廳後抹地
Take your break later.
稍後再休息吧
Piece of shit. Pick up.
人渣  端菜
Where the hell is he?
他在哪兒
- I wanted to check the slot for a work car. - So did I.
- 我查看車場  看車是否仍在那兒  - 我也去
Yeah?
是我
Hang on.
等一等
- Yeah. - Hey.
- 喂  - 嘿
Use a landline. Call me at 103-7206.
用普通電話  撥號103-7206
All right.
好的
- Where are you? - There's cops all over me, man.
- 你在哪兒  - 到處有警察監視我
They're on me like a cheap suit. I can't dump them.
我無法擺脫他們
- After the fact you spotted them? - No, no. They're doing parallels.
- 他們知道你發現他們了嗎  - 不  沒有  他們平衡緊帖我
I can try to dump them again.
我再試試擺脫他們
How are we gonna know if you did? If you didn't, you'll draw them to us.
我怎麼知道你是否擺脫了  你會引他們過來找到我們
Head for Ventura. Pull them out of here.
到宏杜拿去  引開他們
All right. Hey, I'm sorry, man. Last thing I wanna do is let you down.
好的  對不起  我真不想讓你失望
Come on, man.
快點
Pick up.
端出去
- Hey, hey, Neil, man. What up? - What's up, brother?
- 嘿  尼爾  你好嗎  - 你好嗎  兄弟
Man, what you doing here?
你在這兒做什麼
What I am doing is I'm looking for a driver who can handle scanners and a radio.
我在找能夠應付警方追蹤的司機
Right now, today.
現在便要
You remember the drill?
你還記得嗎
Yeah, man, sure.
記得
You cool?
你可靠嗎
Oh, man, now, you know I'm cool.
你知道我很可靠
One answer, yes or no. Right now.
你現在便答覆我  肯或不肯
Yeah, man. Fuck, yeah. You're on.
好的  去它的  我答應
Out back in five.
五分鐘後到後面來
- What's burning? What's burning? - Nothing I'm doing.
- 是什麼燒焦了  - 不是我幹的
What is this?
是什麼事
Where do you think you're going?
你要去哪兒
Just came across a first edition of Kandinsky's Theory of Color.
剛好超過第一版的康丁斯基的色彩理論
Yeah. No, it's in good condition.
是啊  情況很好
And it will not stop or answer radio communication.
這艘船沒有停下  也沒有回覆警方的喊話
The 180-foot vessel is called Jin Yin Number 1...
編號為一八零的這艘船被稱為金銀一號
...and is suspected of smuggling Chinese illegal aliens.
涉嫌偷渡中國非法移民
It was spotted Saturday by patrol aircraft.
警方的巡邏機於星期六發現了這艘可疑船隻
- Stay down. - Don't move! Don't fucking move!
- 趴下  - 別動  不許動
Put your hands in the air! Put your hands in the air! Put them up!
舉起手來  舉起你們的雙手
Down, down! Get on your knees.
趴下  兩腿著地
- Give me the keys. - Get on your knees.
- 把鑰匙給我  - 跪下
Get on your knees!
跪下
Hey. Hey! Get over there. Get the fuck... Get down.
過去那邊  趴下
Turn around! Put your hands behind you. Behind you!
轉身  把手放在背後
Get down! Stay down!
趴下
Get down! Get down! Down, you stupid son of a...
趴下  混蛋
- Down! Down, now! - Keys! Keys! Keys!
- 趴下  - 拿鎖匙來
All of you stay down.
別動
We want to hurt no one. We're here for the bank's money, not your money.
我們不想傷人  只要銀行的錢  不是你們的錢
Your money's insured. You're not gonna lose a dime.
你們不會損失  政府購買了保險
Think of your families. Don't risk your life. Don't try and be a hero.
想想你的家人  別冒生命危險  別逞能
Right now I want you to sit on the floor and put your hands on your head.
我要你們都坐在地上  手放在頭上
Anybody feels sick, anybody got heart trouble, go ahead and lean against the wall.
如果感到不舒服或著心臟難受  便靠在牆上
- Give me the key. - What key?
- 給我鎖匙  - 什麼鎖匙
Get down and stay down!
坐下  別動
Sit there. Sit there. Don't move. Let it bleed.
坐著別動  讓傷口流血吧
Get down!
趴下
Hey. Hey!
嘿
Put your head down.
把頭低下
- Look at me again, I'll kill you. - Stay down. Down.
- 再看我一眼  我就殺了你  - 趴下
- Put your head down! - Get down. Get down.
- 把頭低下  - 低頭  低頭
- Hey, Casals. - Yeah.
- 嘿  卡索斯  - 怎麼啦
You guys working a case on a Neil McCauley?
你們在調查麥·尼爾的案子吧
This CI, Hugh Benny, called in about a bank they're looking at or something.
機密線人許·班尼打來電話  說了關於搶劫銀行的事
Vincent.
雲信
Far East National Bank, 11:30!
早上十一時半  遠東國家銀行
I want a block at Figueroa and 5th...
在第五街交界設路障
...and I want a block northbound Flower at 6th.
花街及第六界北行亦設路障
They're already coming out.
他們出來了
Okay, we're gonna have to take them in the car. Wait till they are all in.
好的  要在車上捉他們  等他們全上車後再動手
Get clean shots. Watch your background.
要利落地射殺他們  別傷及無辜
- Police! Move! - What's going on?
- 警察  走開  - 怎麼回事
Move. Move. Get down.
閃開  趴下
Look out.
小心
- Move it, come on. - L.A.P.D. Get down.
- 讓開  - 洛城警局  趴下
Move it. Down, down, down.
走開  趴下
We did it, right, Neil? Huh?
我們成功了  尼爾
Move!
走開
Get down.
趴下
Fuck. Fuck!
該死
In the car!
開車
Go! Go! Go!
走
- Son of a bitch! - Go, go!
- 混賬東西  - 快走
Go!
走
快走
Come on. Come on.
快起來  走
Get him out of here.
帶他離開這兒
Get down! Now!
趴下
Shit.
見鬼
Out of the way! Down! Out of the way! Get them down! Now, now!
離開這兒  快趴下
No, out of the way. Out of the way.
離開這兒
Mommy? Mommy!
媽咪  媽咪
Come here, honey.
過來  寶貝
Come on, honey.
來吧  孩子
I got you. It's okay now.
我抱著你  沒事兒了
Tragedy in a Southland neighborhood today. A bank robbery spilled out into the street.
今天發生慘劇  銀行劫案禍延街頭
Claudia Newman, live on the scene. She has the latest. Claudia?
鈕·歌迪現時在現場作最新報導
This afternoon, this neighborhood was terrorized by a bank holdup gone wrong.
今天下午  搶劫銀行未遂使這兒很可怕
With the streets full of mid-day shoppers and kids, police and armed robbers...
街上滿是行人和孩子  警方和武裝劫匪激烈交火
- Excuse me, bartender? - One minute, lady.
- 勞駕  酒保  - 這就來  女士
...robbery, pursuit and, finally, death.
新聞提要  劫匪逃走終於死亡
A Los Angeles neighborhood is shaken by a bank robbery...
銀行劫案震動洛杉磯地區
...that ended in homicide and terror.
最後以兇殺及恐懼告終
One suspect, Michael Cheritto, is one of four men involved in the foiled robbery.
查·米高是四名劫匪之一
- He died at the scene. - What can I get you, miss?
- 他在現場死去  - 喝點什麼  小姐
Also fatally wounded, suspect Donald Breedan...
另一個受重傷的疑匪  當·畢頓
Miss?
小姐
...during the extensive gunfire between police and suspects.
在警方和劫匪交火時  中槍身亡
All right, hold him. Hold him.
好了  按著他
- All right. All right. - It's all right.
- 沒事兒的  - 沒事兒了
- So? - Well, he's got blood loss and shock.
- 情況怎樣  - 他失血過多  驚嚇過度
I'm gonna give you quarter-grain morphine for the pain. Subcutaneous injection.
我給你最少量的嗎啡止痛
Bottom line.
告訴我吧
It's mostly tissue damage, which is good, but his clavicle's fractured.
主要是組織受損  那是好事  他的鎖骨折斷
- Can he rest for a while? - Six, seven hours.
- 能讓他休息嗎  - 六七個小時
- That's it? - That's it.
- 不能多留嗎  - 不能
- Take off your shirt. - What?
- 脫下你的襯衣  - 什麼
Take off your shirt.
脫下你的襯衣
My... Look, my daughter gave it to me for Father's Day.
這是女兒在父親節送給我的
I don't give a shit who gave it to you. Take it off.
我不管  脫下來
Chris. Hey.
基斯  嘿
Chris, listen to me.
聽著
Nate's gonna pick you up. He's gonna take you to his place.
奈德會接你  送你到他家中
- Where's Charlene? - We gotta get out of here.
- 莎蓮呢  - 我們得離開這兒
We're all over the 6:00 news.
新聞一直在播銀行的事
- We gotta get out of here. - I'm not going without her.
- 我們必須得走  - 沒有她我不走
Think about that. I will meet you at Nate's.
你考慮一下  在奈德那兒見
Where are you going?
你去哪兒
I gotta find out if our out got spilled along with every other damn thing.
查探逃走路線是否給洩露了
Who did it?
是誰告密的
Who wasn't there?
有誰沒參加
Trejo.
齊祖
I'll see you at Nate's.
在奈德家見
- Yeah. - Yeah. You still want me?
- 是的  - 你仍想要我嗎
You come down here right now and you get me. Dominick and me. Okay?
你來這裏接我和多明吧
Okay, baby, okay. I'll be there in two hours, all right?
好的  寶貝  我兩小時後到
- Okay? - All right.
- 好嗎  - 好吧
Goddamn you, Chris. Goddamn you.
你真該死  基斯  你真該死
- You're on a plane for Los Angeles. - Great.
- 你坐飛機前往洛杉磯  - 太好了
Why'd you do it? What happened?
你為何這樣做  怎麼回事
- They made me. - Who?
- 他們逼迫我  - 誰
Where's Anna?
安娜呢
She's dead.
她死了
So is Michael and Breedan, the guy who stood in for you.
米高和代替你的畢頓亦死了
- Who did it? Who did it? - They had Anna, man.
- 誰迫害你的  是誰 -  他們威脅安娜
Who had her?
誰威脅她
Waingro.
榮谷
On his own?
他一個人嗎
- For someone. - Who?
- 替人賣命  - 誰
The other he worked for.
他替別人工作
Zant.
宏山
- Van Zant? - Yeah.
- 宏山  - 對
Van Zant.
宏山
- Are you sure? - Van Zant.
- 你肯定嗎  - 宏山
Did you say anything about how we're getting out?
你有說出我們怎樣逃走嗎
- I don't think so, Neil. - Come on.
- 我認為沒有  - 說吧
I don't remember, Neil.
我不記得了
- I'll call a medic. - I'm not gonna make it.
- 我通知救護員  - 我無法活下去的
I can't feel nothing.
我全無感覺
My Anna's gone.
我的安娜死了
She's gone.
她死了
Don't leave me like this, Neil. Please, holmes.
別這樣扔下我  尼爾  求求你  朋友
Don't leave me like this.
別這樣扔下我
- Yeah? - Nate.
- 喂  - 奈德
You on a cellular? Use a hard line.
你用無線電話嗎  用普通電話
It's a new one.
這是新的電話
The guy lives on Hillside Terrace, Encino.
他住在安僊奴區山景台
- 10725. - 10725, okay.
- 一零七二五號  - 一零七二五號  好的
- Chris? - He's with me, at my place.
- 基斯呢  - 他和我一起在我家中
Next, Waingro, okay?
跟著查出榮谷在哪兒
You got the time?
你有時間嗎
I'll make time, and I need a new out laid on.
我會抽空的  我需要新的逃走路線
How do you know it's blown?
你怎麼知道被洩露了呢
How can I trust it?
我怎麼能相信沒洩露呢
Okay, you got it.
好的  沒問題
Stay healthy.
保住性命
Charlene Shiherlis.
莎蓮
Drucker's got a safe house in Venice to stash her in.
澤加在威尼斯區有地方收藏她
Our Neil's transportation. When we're done here, get on the phone.
尼爾的逃走方法
Somewhere, someone's trying to put it together for him.
正有人替他安排一切
You don't believe McCauley already had a getaway?
你不會認為他已經有計劃了吧
Sure he did. Now he needs another one. Would you trust yours after this afternoon?
他當然有計劃  但他需要另一個計劃  換成你還能相信原來的計劃嗎
This rat motherfucker, where did we get him?
這告密的混蛋  哪兒找到他的
He's a CI for a burglary cop. Called in the tip on the bank.
他是機密線人  通報劫銀行線索
On Neil McCauley, how much time we got?
談談麥·尼爾吧  還有多少時間
Eight, 10 hours for him to set up a new out. After that, he's gone.
他有八至十小時安排新逃走路線  之後  他就走了
Bye-bye. Bam.
拜拜了
You ratted McCauley to us. How'd you know? Who told you?
你向我們告發麥·尼爾  你怎麼知道  誰告訴你的
Who told you, you rat motherfucker?
是誰告訴你的  混蛋
Who?
是誰
Connelly back in for Murphy. Murphy with Leggat right there with him.
康尼回來阻擊墨菲  墨菲在奮力拼搶
Murphy tees it up behind the net...
得球後  準備打門
...Miller out front. Now here's Murphy with the referee...
米勒也衝到了前場
Waingro, where is he?
榮谷在哪兒
- Where is he? - How the hell would I know?
- 在哪兒  - 我怎麼知道
Well, what do we have here, hmm?
嗯  這兒有些什麼
Isn't this pretty? It's pretty.
這兒漂亮嗎  漂亮嗎
- You slimy piece of shit. - You told me you wanted out from under.
- 你這個小人  - 你告訴我想脫離目前的困境
You're scared to death, right? You want out? This is out, Charlene.
你想脫身嗎  這是出路
- Yeah, what's your end? - I... You stupid broad.
- 你得到什麼好處啦  - 我沒好處  你這個蠢娘們
- How'd I get into this? - Hey, hey, hey. Easy.
- 我怎麼會牽涉此事的  - 嘿  冷靜  別衝動
You heard me.
你聽到我說的了
She had a rough ride. Why don't you fix her a drink or something?
她已經夠難受的了  你為何不給她倒杯酒呢
- Look in the cabinet above the sink. - Fuck her.
- 到櫥櫃看看  - 去她的
- You'd better get in there and stay in there. - All right, all right.
- 你最好進去  不要出來  - 好吧
Well, lookie here.
看看這兒
My name is Sergeant Drucker, L.A.P.D. Homicide.
我是澤加  洛城警局  兇殺組探員
- You wanna put Dominick in the bedroom? - He stays with me.
- 要送多明進睡房嗎  - 他和我待在一起
There we go.
坐下
So, what now?
現在怎麼辦
Well, he's right, because you want out, this is out.
他說得對  你想脫身  這是出路
- You believe you have to betray Chris. - No shit.
- 你真的要出賣基斯嗎  - 正是
That's right. You would have to.
這就對了  你是得這樣做
See, if you don't betray Chris, you victimize Dominick.
若不出賣基斯  多明會是受害人
Because he becomes an orphan when you go to prison as an accessory...
因為當你入獄時  他便會成為孤兒
...because you got no living parents to take him.
你也沒有父母來照顧他
So he ends up state-raised in foster homes, juvenile facilities.
他會被送進收養所  青少年中心
Then he steals a car.
之後他會偷車
Then he winds up in gladiator academies like Chino and Tracy.
然後入獄學會做真正的罪犯
Fucked for life.
毀了一生
You know what happens, because you've been there.
你是過來人  知道會有何下場
Dominick didn't get a chance yet to choose his life, but Chris did.
多明沒機會選擇生活  但基斯有
If you give up Chris, you get off clean.
你若供出基斯  你會沒有案底
You can do it for your kid, so you can raise him.
你可以為了孩子而這樣做  你可以撫養他
- What else are you selling? - All kinds of shit.
- 你還有什麼條件  - 各種各樣的東西
But I don't have to sell this and you know it, because this kind of shit here sells itself.
但我不用說服你  因為我是對的
Okay, Danny, here's an update.
最新消息
- Drucker's on Line 2. - Lieutenant, hold on for a second.
- 澤加在二線  - 等一等
Lieutenant, I have Drucker on the other line.
澤加在另一電話線
Oh, well, conference him in.
三人通話吧
- Go ahead. - Vincent, it's me.
- 說吧  - 雲信  是我
I want an answer. What's it gonna be?
你的答覆是怎樣的
We're set here. She'll make the call.
我們準備好了  她會打電話
Okay, that's good. Here's the deal here.
好的  情況是這樣
Hugh Benny has reformed his wayward life and become a born-again good citizen.
許·班尼已改過自新  成為洗心革面的好市民
Apparently, Neil got sold out to us by this cowboy named Waingro.
叫榮谷的人向我們出賣了尼爾
Waingro used to be a part of Neil's crew...
榮谷曾是他手下
...then he went to work for a money launderer named Van Zant.
後替洗錢人工作  他叫宏山
Units are at Van Zant's house as we speak because he got shot dead earlier tonight.
現時正派人前住宏山家中  因為他今晚較早前被殺
Now, if Neil goes after anybody else, it's gonna be Waingro.
尼爾要對付的人會是榮谷
Waingro just got himself a suite at the airport Marquis...
榮谷正入住侯爵機場酒店套房
...under the name "Jameson". He's there now.
並化名詹美臣  他正在那兒
I want you to get that to bail bondsmen, bookies...
我要你把這消息告訴外圍帶家
...assignment officers and snitches in County.
奉派警員及線人
Anyone you can think of who'll put it on the street.
任何能把消息外洩的人
Deploy a team at the hotel and personally check their come every 30 minutes.
派人到酒店駐守  並每隔半小時收聽無線電
Because maybe Neil will go for him. Okay? How you feeling?
也許尼爾會殺他  明白嗎  你感覺怎麼樣
- Banged up, but I'll live. - Okay.
- 不算太慘  我會活著  - 很好
He's here.
他仍在
Neil is still here.
尼爾還沒走
I can feel it.
我能感覺到
But for how long?
會留多久
Seven, eight hours, max.
最多七八個小時
What did you do?
你做過什麼
- That was you? - It's what I don't do, I don't sell metal.
- 是你做的嗎  - 我不是賣金屬的
Would have been okay, you fly out after. Now it's jammed.
計劃原本順利  但現在出了麻煩
- Now we gotta go together. - Those other people were with you?
- 我們要一起走  - 那些人和你一起的嗎
My friend, Michael...
我的朋友米高
...he knew the risks. He didn't have to be there.
他知道所冒的險
It rains, you get wet.
身處險境便要冒生命危險
Get packed and let's go.
收拾東西
Eady.
伊荻
Why did you do this to me?
你為何這樣對我
Who are you?
你究竟是誰
It's gonna be all right. You understand? It'll be all right.
不會有事的  明白嗎
It's gonna be all right.
不會有事的
Right.
不會的
There's this Camaro at this address, Level D, Slot 18.
這個地址  D層十八單位  有一輛汽車
Here's some cash.
這兒有現金
When's it over?
此事何時瞭解
22 hours from now.
二十二小時後
- Then we get out of here clean. - When will you let me leave?
- 那時我們便可脫身  - 那時你會讓我離開嗎
Go now. You want out? There's the door.
那現在就走吧  你想離開嗎  門在那邊
Will you let me leave later?
你稍後會讓我離開嗎
It will be different.
情況會不同
Do you understand?
你還不明白嗎
It's ready.
準備好了
Vincent.
雲信
This is my friend Ralph.
這是我的朋友洛夫
You didn't tell me you were...
你沒說你已已經
- Oh, my God. - Where's Lauren?
- 天啊  - 羅蘭在哪兒
- She's at Lisa-Beth's. - Look, this has nothing to do with me.
- 她在碧芙家中  - 聽著  此事和我無關
- I didn't know. I'm terribly sorry. - What are you sorry about? Sit down.
- 我不知道  對不起  - 對不起什麼  坐下
Don't you even get angry?
你不生氣嗎
I'm angry, yeah.
我當然生氣
I'm very angry, Ralph.
我非常生氣  洛夫
You know, you can ball my wife if she wants you to.
若她想要你干她  你可以干我太太
You can lounge around here on her sofa.
你可以躺在她的沙發上
In her ex-husband's...
在她前夫的
...dead-tech, post-modernistic, bullshit house, if you want to...
高科技後現代主義的荒謬家中  若你想的話
...but you do not get to watch my fucking television set!
但你不能看我該死的電視機
For God's sake.
天啊
Put the television set down.
把電視機放下
- I never cheated on you, bitch. - Maybe you should have.
- 我沒對你不忠  賤貨  - 也許你應該
- I should have? - In a way, you're a party to this.
- 我應該嗎  - 你對此也有責任
Oh, yeah. I made Ralph fuck you because it makes me feel good.
沒錯  我要洛夫干你  因為這使我開心
Our situation is absurd.
我們的處境荒謬
- Look, maybe I should... - Shut up, Ralph. Sit down!
- 聽著  也許我該走了  - 住口  洛夫  坐下
Why is it that I have to figure things out and explain them to you? What do you do?
我為何要向你把事情解釋清楚  你又做什麼了
- I say what I mean, and I do what I say. - Mm, how admirable.
- 我說話算話  亦言出必行  - 哼  多麼可敬
- You bet. - Except none of it's about us.
- 那當然  - 可是沒什麼是和我們有關的
No.
是的
I may be stoned on grass and Prozac...
我一定是抽大麻或服興奮劑迷糊了
...but you've been walking through our life dead.
但你在我們的生活中猶如死了
Now I have to demean myself with Ralph just to get closure with you.
我不得不作踐自己  找洛夫來終斷我們的關係
Passports, traveler's checks, plastic.
護照  旅行支票  信用卡
The plane, charter terminal, LAX, Hangar 17.
這飛機  在洛城機場包機站十七號機庫
Call letters are 1011 Sierra.
確定密碼是一零一一山嶺
Touches down, holds for you five minutes, then splits.
飛機會降落  等你五分鐘  然後便起飛
The plane will stand an FAA check. Filed a flight plan, the works.
飛機會通過航空局檢查等手續
- Hey, where's Chris? - He's gone.
- 基斯呢  - 他走了
What?
什麼
Said he's going on his own. Went to look for Charlene.
他說去找莎蓮  他走了
- Didn't you bring him here? - Yeah, I brought him here.
- 是你帶他來這兒的嗎  - 是的  我帶他來了
What happened?
怎麼回事
It's a free country, brother.
這是個自由國家
Check in with me at 9. Everything's still cool.
晚上九時聯絡我  確保一切妥當
All right.
好的
I don't even know what I'm doing anymore.
我甚至不知道自己在做什麼
I know life is short.
我知道人生苦短
Whatever time you get is luck.
能活多久是運氣
You wanna walk?
你想終斷這段關係
You walk right now.
你現在就能離開
Or on your own...
或者你自願
On your own, you choose to come with me.
你自願選擇跟我一起走
All I know is...
我只知道
All I know is there's no point in me going anywhere anymore...
我無論到任何地方去  都將失去意義
...if it's gonna be alone...
因為只有我獨自一人
...without you.
沒有你陪在身邊
Eady.
伊荻
- Yeah. - Yeah, Vincent, I got a live one.
- 喂  - 雲信  我抓了個活的
Okay, I'll hold.
好  我等著
Come on, sugar. Show yourself.
過去  讓基斯看見你
- Yeah, do it. - Shut up!
- 快去啊  - 住口
Now, just one second at the window...
只需在窗前站一秒
...and it's all over.
此事便會了結
Hey, man.
朋友
- Yeah? - You know any, uh...
- 幹嘛  - 你知道
...place to rent around here?
這附近有地方要出租嗎
Yeah.
知道
Alberiz's Grocer on Dell Avenue got cards on the wall.
那邊牆上有告示
Yeah, thanks.
好的  謝謝
It's not him. It's not Chris.
不是他  不是基斯
Unit 2, this is Command.
是指揮部
Take him at the street and check him out.
攔住他  核實他的身份
10-4.
收到
- Sergeant? - Yeah.
- 警官  - 說
This guy's John Peterson. Valid ID.
他叫莊·彼得  有效的身份證
Car's registered to the last name Bukowski, first name Gene.
車輛登記人是布·基贊
Ran it to DMV. It's clean.
向運輸署查核過  沒有不妥
- Let him go. - Roger.
- 讓他走  - 收到
Thank you very much. Have a good evening.
非常感謝  祝你晚安
It's a no-go, Vince.
不是他  雲信
Would you like a cup of coffee while we wait, Mrs. Shiherlis?
我們等時你想喝咖啡嗎
Yeah, that'd be nice.
那會很不錯
- Yeah? - Yeah, what do you got?
- 喂  - 你有什麼消息
Nothing's happening.
沒事發生
- Yeah? - Hello, it's Vincent.
- 喂  - 我是雲信
What do you got?
有何動靜
Nothing's going on. Waingro went for ice. That's it.
沒有  榮谷去拿冰塊了
You know what?
你知道嗎
Neil is gone.
尼爾跑了
Bam!
走了
- Flying like a bird. - Come on, Vincent, how do you know?
- 像鳥兒般飛走  - 行了  雲信  你怎麼知道
- We still got bait. Maybe some time! - Got, got. What do we got?
- 我們還有機會  也許仍有時間  - 得了  我們有什麼
What do we got?
我們有什麼
Bon voyage, motherfucker.
一路順風  混蛋
You were good.
你很了不起
I'm going to the hotel.
我要回酒店去
I'm gonna take a shower.
我要洗澡
Gonna sleep for a month.
好好睡覺  睡一個月
Over here.
來
Come on, baby.
醒來吧
Okay, okay.
好了
Shit.
不要
Let me tighten this.
讓我綁緊胳膊
What a fucking waste.
浪費生命
Okay, here.
好了  來了
Assholes shoot themselves all fucking day. Not you, baby. Not you.
每天都有混蛋自殺  但你不是混蛋  寶貝  你不會死的
Where would she be? Her name is Lauren, Lauren Gustafson.
她會在哪兒  她叫羅蘭  古·羅蘭
I'm supposed to be here with her. But the police...
她該在這兒的
- Help me. I need somebody to help... - It's okay.
- 我要人幫忙  - 沒事兒的
I got you.
我抱著你
I got you, baby.
我抱著你呢  寶貝
It'll be all right, honey. I swear. It's okay, baby.
你會沒事的  你會沒事的  寶貝
Let's get a doctor! Let's go! A doctor here! There's your mama.
快找醫生來  你媽媽來了
- Let's just calm down. - Your mama's here.
- 冷靜下來  - 你媽媽在這兒
- Is she on any drugs? - No.
- 她是吸毒了嗎  - 不是
I want you to get a trauma surgeon and a vascular surgeon.
找精神創傷及血管醫生來
I think she cut both arteries. Also, I could hardly feel her pulse.
她割斷了兩條動脈  我摸不到她的脈搏
Her pressure's down. So is her respiration. You have to intubate her.
她的血壓很低  呼吸也很微弱  要給她插管
It's ready.
準備好了
- When's the last time anybody saw her? - I don't know.
- 最後一次見她時是什麼時候  - 我不知道
- Where did you find her? - The bathtub.
- 你在哪兒找到她的  - 浴缸
Call Respiratory stat. Give her large-bore normal saline. Wide open.
給她注射大針管的鹽水
Let's keep pressure on those bleeders. I need two units, O-negative.
緊按出血的血管  先輸入兩個單位O型血
- Let's type and cross her for six. - Looks like she's in sinus tach.
- 查明血型後再輸入六個單位相同的  - 看來她已經竇性心律過速
Where is Respiratory? We need more help.
呼吸專家呢  我們需要幫忙
Can you have Respiratory come now?
快叫呼吸科醫生過來
Let's have x-ray ready for post-intubation chest x-ray.
準備插管後照X光
Hi. Your daughter's out of surgery and she's in the recovery room now, okay?
嗨  你的女兒已經做好手術  正在療養室
Her vital signs are stable. The surgeon will be out to speak to you in a few moments.
她情況穩定  醫生很快會跟你說
- She's okay? - She's doing good.
- 她沒事吧  - 她很好
- She's gonna be okay. - She's gonna be okay.
- 她會好起來的  - 她會好起來的
- Oh, my baby. - She's gonna be okay. It's all right.
- 噢  我的寶貝  - 她會好起來的  沒事了
- It's all right. - Why'd she do this to herself? Why?
- 沒事了  - 她為何這樣對待自己
Look what she did. Look what she did to herself.
看她把自己怎麼了
There.
好了
It's all right, honey. It's gonna be all right.
沒事的  不會有事的
I'm here. I ain't going anywhere.
我在這兒  不會到別處去
- You understand? - Yeah.
- 明白嗎  - 嗯
I ain't going anywhere.
我不會到別處去
Yeah?
喂
It's me.
是我
Plane's in the air now. It'll be right on time.
飛機已在半空  你得準時到達
On the driver's end, I still can't find nobody, so that's in the trust.
可信任的司機仍找不到
One other thing.
還有一事
You asked, so I gotta tell you.
你問過我  所以我得告訴你
The guy you wanted checked into the Marquis under "Jameson"...
你找的人在候爵酒店  化名詹美臣
...if you still give a shit, which I figured you wouldn't.
我看你不想找他了吧
- You figured right. - So, so long, brother.
- 你說得對  - 那麼  再見  兄弟
You take it easy.
多保重
You're home free.
你自由了
Take it easy.
你也保重
- What is it? - Nothing.
- 什麼事  - 沒事
Home free.
自由了
- I gotta take care of something. - Is there time?
- 我得解決一些事情  - 還有時間嗎
There's time.
有的
I'll be right back. Just leave her running.
我很快回來  讓車子開動吧
- Registration. - Yeah, this is Room Service.
- 入住登記處  - 我是房間餐飲部
A Jameson ordered a BLT. They screwed up his room number. Could you give it to me?
詹美臣要了食物  但房號弄錯了  你能告訴我嗎
- They're always doing that. - Yeah, I know.
- 他們經常會弄錯  - 我知道
- 1735. - Thank you.
- 是一七三五號房  - 謝謝
Your attention, please.
請注意
We are currently experiencing a fire alarm.
現在響起火警警報
Please do not panic. Please do not take the elevators.
不用惶恐  不要乘坐升降機
Shit. Waingro's not moving. I'm staying here.
該死  榮谷沒走  我留在這兒
I'm checking the stairs. If there's smoke, I'm pulling you out.
我查看樓梯  若有煙  便會要你走
What about her dad? You want me to call him?
我該通知她父親嗎
He's somewhere in the Sierras.
他在內華達山脈某處
And she chose you.
她選擇了你
She picked your place.
選擇在你的房間自殺
It's not right, what happened to her.
這樣做是不對的  不該發生在她身上
No, it's not.
是的
Ugh, okay.
好了
Is there any way...
是否有方法
...that it could work out between us?
能克服我們之間的問題
I wish I could say yes, you know.
我希望說有
But in the end...
可是  到最後
You know, it's like you said:
就像你說的
All I am, is what I'm going after.
我沉迷於  追捕我的罪犯
I'm not what you want, Justine.
我不是你想要的人
Well, go on, if you have to.
若你要走  便走吧
No.
不
- I'll stay. - No, I'm okay. I can... I can handle this.
- 我會留下  - 我沒事  我可以應付
Just be careful.
你保重
Call me here. Let me know you're okay.
給我打電話  讓我知道你沒事
Okay?
好嗎
Take the stairs.
走樓梯
Yeah?
幹嘛
Security. There's a fire on 3. We have to evacuate all the floors.
酒店保安  三樓發生火警  各樓層的人都要疏散
I can't leave here.
我不能離開
Why don't we just talk about this a bit, huh, brother?
我們何不先談一下  兄弟
He's here on 17.
他在十七樓
Look at me. Look at me.
看著我  看著我
Look at me.
看著我
L.A.P.D. Don't move. Put your hands on your head, now.
洛城警方  別動  把手放在頭上
Switch me to TAC 5.
將我轉到五號頻道
Casals? JJ?
卡索斯  JJ
Drucker, JJ?
澤加  JJ
I'm at the lobby level by the stairwell.
我在大堂接近樓梯井
What have you got?
出了什麼事
Teams are moving up the other elevators to the 17th floor elevators.
小組搭乘另一升降機前往十七樓
All out of commission because of the fire alarm.
因為火警警鐘響起  升降機不能用
- It's a mess. People everywhere. - Fine. 10-4.
- 這裏一團糟  人山人海  - 好的  知道了
Let's go, get out of the way.
快走  不要擋道
Stay out of the way.
不要擋道
Let's go. Go that way. We gotta go, all right? Go, go.
快走  快離開
I got it, sir.
讓我來  先生
Come on, come on.
快走
Come on, sir.
快走  先生
- Watch your backs, ladies. - I got it, I got it.
- 小心後面  女士們  - 我搞定了
Keep moving, ma'am.
繼續走  夫人
Let's go.
走吧
Come on, let's go.
快點  走吧
This way, ma'am.
走這邊  夫人
Get back, get back.
後退  後退
- Let me have that shotgun. - Yes, sir.
- 把槍給我  - 是  長官
Told you I'm never going back.
跟你說過  我不會再回到監獄
Yeah.
是啊